nagarro.com 2014-06-02

# Privacy Policy | Nagarro

This Privacy Statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. This Privacy Policy applies to all websites and web pages owned by Nagarro, Inc. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at [info at nagarro doc com](mailto:info@nagarro.com)

We may collect the following types of information: your IP address and information you provide through sign-up forms on our web pages. We may combine this information with information from other services or third parties in order to administer our site, to track your usage across our website and to improve the quality and relevance of our content based on the features and content people use most often.

When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including logging in to the service, storing user preferences, maintaining report selection, and tracking your web page visits. We may also use cookies to personally identify you so that we can understand each individual visitor’s actions on our website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not. If you have enabled “Do Not Track” functionality in your web browser, then your personally identifiable cookies will expire within 5 days.

This site gives users the following option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: To delete your record from our database, send us an email at [info at nagarro dot com](mailto:info@nagarro.com) with the subject: ‘Unsubscribe from mailing list’

To modify information previously provided: Send email to [info at nagarro dot com](mailto:info@nagarro.com) to request a change with the subject: “Change Contact Information”.

This site contains links to other sites. Nagarro is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

Nagarro reserves the right to modify or update our Privacy Policy at any time without notice, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time.
